[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In May 2004 the European Union accepted 10 new countries. Which of them was first to adopt the Euro as its national currency?", "correct_answer": "Slovenia", "incorrect_answers": ["Poland", "Slovakia", "Estonia"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This exotic cat breed was developed in Kenya by crossbreeding between a Serval and a domestic cat.", "correct_answer": "Savannah", "incorrect_answers": ["Bengal", "Maine Coon", "Egyptian Mau"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "If the world were a village of 100 people, how many would own a computer?", "correct_answer": "1", "incorrect_answers": ["5", "15", "11"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these magazines came first?", "correct_answer": "Boys Life", "incorrect_answers": ["Highlights for Children", "Playboy", "Discover"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of the Peruvian floating islands, located in Lake Titicaca?", "correct_answer": "Uros", "incorrect_answers": ["Chaka", "Laka", "Barro"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Island coffees are some of the smoothest and most expensive in the world. Where do they come from?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Hawaii", "Jamaica", "St. Helena"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "A windspeed of 100 feet above the ground was observed in 1999 in what Oklahoma city?", "correct_answer": "Moore", "incorrect_answers": ["Lawton", "Norman", "Midwest City"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This helicopter was used widely by the U. S. military during the Vietnam War.", "correct_answer": "Huey", "incorrect_answers": ["Pavelow", "Apache", "Cobra"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What does the name of the zebra literally mean?", "correct_answer": "Wild ass", "incorrect_answers": ["Funny horse", "Striped", "Black-and-white"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these Academy Awards did the 1995 drama Braveheart NOT win?", "correct_answer": "Costume Design", "incorrect_answers": ["Best Picture", "Best Director", "Best Makeup"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What signature object does Hellboy always have in his mouth in 2008s Hellboy II: The Golden Army?", "correct_answer": "A Cigar", "incorrect_answers": ["Nothing", "A Beer Bottle", "A Piece of Wheat"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the rating of the 2007 film Ghost Rider according to The Motion Picture Association of Americas standards?", "correct_answer": "PG-13", "incorrect_answers": ["PG", "R", "G"]}]